#### Contact

S/o: N.Rameya Reddy At/po: Kotharshing Via: Golanthare Dist: Ganjam, Odisha, Pin: 761008 +91 9583996098 (Mobile) Ireddy563@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/n-lohidasureddy (LinkedIn) www.lreddy563blogspot.com (Blog)

#### Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Programming
DevOps

#### Certifications

Amazon Web Services Developer - Associate

# N.Lohidasu Reddy

Senior Linux/Cloud/DevOps Engineer at Capsule8 Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

### Summary

Working as a Cloud/DevOps Engineer @capsule8. With hands-on experience on all the tools like: GIT, SVN, Jenkins (Maven Integration, SonarQube Integration, Jfrog Integration, Tomcat deployment, and Selenium Integration), Ansible, Docker, Terraform, Vagrant.

Also, worked as a JIRA Admin(Project Creation, Workflow Desing, Notification Setting, and Security Settings) and AWS Cloud Engineer(EC2, EBS, S3, VPC, ELB, IAM, DynomoDB, RDS, and other services).

# Experience

Capsule8
Cloud Operations Engineer
August 2019 - Present (8 months)
Chennai Area, India

Dell India R&D Center Private Limited DevOps Engineer December 2018 - August 2019 (9 months) Bangalore

TechDynamic Software Engineer September 2014 - November 2018 (4 years 3 months) Bangaon Area, India

#### Education

Vignan Institute of Technology And Management Bachelor In Technical Education, Electrical & Electronis Engineering · (2010 - 2014)

## Berhampur City College

+2 Science, Biology, Maths, Physics and Chemistry · (2008 - 2010)

## Biswanath High And Technical School

Matriculation · (2004 - 2008)